Guide to the Horace Walpole Collection
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Horace Walpole's Correspondence, 1725-1797; Series I; 12
  - Mann, Sir Horatio, 1st Baronet *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Feb 13 (Box 26, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 458-59.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Mar 6 (Box 26, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 463-64.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Mar 30 (Box 26, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 467-70.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Apr 24 (Box 26, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 472-74.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 May 4 (Box 26, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 476-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 May 15 (Box 26, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 478-80.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Jun 8 (Box 26, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 485-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Jun 19 (Box 26, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 492-93.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Jul 13 (Box 26, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 493-95.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Aug 10 (Box 26, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 500-503.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Aug 14 (Box 26, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 503-4.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Aug 24 (Box 26, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 506-8.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Sep 7 (Box 26, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 512-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Sep 21 (Box 26, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 515-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Sep 28 (Box 26, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 517-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Nov 9 (Box 26, Folder 57)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 525-27.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Nov 30 (Box 26, Folder 58)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 531-33.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1773 Dec 18 (Box 26, Folder 59)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 534-36.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Jan 11 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 541-43.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Jan 18 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 544-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Feb 19 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 552-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Mar 12 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 558-59.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Mar 29 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 563-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Apr 23 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 23, p. 565-67.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 May 17 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 6-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 May 28 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 9-12.
    - Letter to Richard Croft, 1774 Jun 7 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Mentioned in letter from Horace Walpole to Horace Mann, 3 Aug. 1774. See note in Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 27, n. 23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Jun 18 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 18-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Jul 26 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 22-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Aug 6 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 28-30.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Aug 23 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 31-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Sep 20 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 39-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Sep 24 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 41-42.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Oct 1 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 42-44.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Oct 8 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 49-51.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Nov 18 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 57-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Nov 22 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 58-59.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Dec 13 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 64-66.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1774 Dec 27 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 68-70.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Jan 21 (Box 27, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 72-74.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Jan 30 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 78-80.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Mar 11 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 83-85.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Apr 8 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 87-89.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Apr 22 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 94-96.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 May 2 (Box 27, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 96-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 May 20 (Box 27, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 104-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 May 31 (Box 27, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 106-8.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Jun 27 (Box 27, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 113-15.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Jul 28 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 117-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Aug 12 (Box 27, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 121-23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Sep 16 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 128-30.
      Letter misdated by Horace Mann.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Sep 30 (Box 27, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 130-32.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Oct 28 (Box 27, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 135-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Nov 4 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 140-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Nov 14 (Box 27, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 144-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Dec 2 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 145-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1775 Dec 30 (Box 27, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 163-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Jan 9 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 165-67.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Jan 13 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 167-71.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Jan 23 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 171-73.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Mar 2 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 180-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Mar 9 (Box 27, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 182-84.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Apr 2 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 188-89.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Apr 13 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 189-91.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 May 4 (Box 27, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 198-201.
      With enclosure: Abstract from a letter to young Sir Horace Mann from Mr. Hull, a lawyer, 15 Mar. 1776.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 May 14 (Box 27, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 202-4.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 May 28 (Box 27, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 213-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Jun 8 (Box 27, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 219-21.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Jun 18 (Box 27, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 221-22.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Jul 13 (Box 27, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 223-26.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Aug 13 (Box 27, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 232-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Sep 7 (Box 27, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 237-39.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Sep 18 (Box 27, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 239-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Oct 12 (Box 27, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 243-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Oct 12 bis (Box 27, Folder 57)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 247-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Oct 19 (Box 27, Folder 58)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 250-52.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Nov 1 (Box 27, Folder 59)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 256-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Nov 16 (Box 27, Folder 60)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 259-60.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1776 Nov 26 (Box 27, Folder 61)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 264-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Jan 7 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 270-72.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Jan 25 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 274-76.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Feb 15 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 279-81.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Mar 11 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 284-86.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Apr 19 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 289-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Apr 26 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 290-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Apr 28 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 296-99.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, Circa 1777 May 16 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 303-4.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Jun 3 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 305-7.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Jun 28 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 311-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Jul 19 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 317-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Aug 16 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 321-22.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Sep 23 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 329-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Nov 11 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 336-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1777 Dec 10 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 343-44.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Jan 3 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 345-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Feb 7 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 351-53.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Feb 24 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 356-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Mar 14 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 362-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Mar 31 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 368-70.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Apr 14 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 373-74.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Apr 28 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 375-76.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 May 30 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 380-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Jun 23 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 388-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Jul 7 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 394-96.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Aug 1 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 396-98.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Aug 22 (Box 28, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 402-5.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Sep 15 (Box 28, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 408-10.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Oct 27 (Box 28, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 416-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Dec 8 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 425.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1778 Dec 19 (Box 28, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 428-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Jan 16 (Box 28, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 433-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Feb 6 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 436-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Feb 15 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 443.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Mar 13 (Box 28, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 452-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Mar 30 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 457-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Apr 17 (Box 28, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 461-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Apr 24 (Box 28, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 466-68.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 May 4 (Box 28, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 468-70.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 May 15 (Box 28, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 476-78.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 May 25 (Box 28, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 478-80.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Jun 19 (Box 28, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 486-88.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Jun 22 (Box 28, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 489.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Jul 3 (Box 28, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 495.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Aug 7 (Box 28, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 504-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Aug 27 (Box 28, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 508-10.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Sep 11 (Box 28, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 513-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Sep 25 (Box 28, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 517-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Oct 16 (Box 28, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 522-23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Nov 13 (Box 28, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 530-32.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1779 Dec 10 (Box 28, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 24, p. 539-42.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Jan 3 (Box 28, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 1-3.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Jan 29 (Box 28, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 8-10.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Feb 12 (Box 28, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 15-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Mar 11 (Box 28, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 22-26.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Mar 31 (Box 28, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 31-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Apr 27 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 42-46.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 May 20 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 49-51.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Jun 10 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 57-61.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Jun 30 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 64-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Jul 8 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 69-73.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Jul 29 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 76-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Aug 26 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 80-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, Circa 1780 Sep 5 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 83-85.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Oct 24 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 93-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Dec 12 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 100-102.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1780 Dec 30 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 106-8.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Jan 13 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 112-13.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Jan 16 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 113-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Jan 27 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 120.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Feb 13 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 127-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Feb 24 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 129-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Feb 28 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 136.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Mar 6 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 136-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Apr 21 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 143-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 May 12 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 149-51.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 May 26 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 155-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Jun 9 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 159-61.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Jul 3 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 161-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Jul 24 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 168-71.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Aug 18 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 173-75.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Sep 1 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 178-79.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Sep 4 (Box 29, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 179-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Sep 22 (Box 29, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 188-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Oct 9 (Box 29, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 192-93.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Oct 25 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 198-200.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Nov 10 (Box 29, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 203-4.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Nov 20 (Box 29, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 204-8.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Dec 13 (Box 29, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 219.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1781 Dec 29 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 228-32.
      With enclosure: Letter from Cavalier Mozzi to Horace Mann, 29 Dec. 1781.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Jan 12 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 233-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Feb 2 (Box 29, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 238-40.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Feb 26 (Box 29, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 248-51.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Apr 13 (Box 29, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 268-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Apr 26 (Box 29, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 270-71.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Apr 30 (Box 29, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 271-72.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Jun 8 (Box 29, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 281-83.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Jul 6 (Box 29, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 290-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Jul 30 (Box 29, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 299-302.
      With enclosure: Copy of a letter from Cavaliere Mozzi to Lord Orford.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Aug 17 (Box 29, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 302-5.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Aug 19 (Box 29, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 305-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Aug 31 (Box 29, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 313-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Sep 15 (Box 29, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 317-19.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Sep 28 (Box 29, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 322-23.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Oct 5 (Box 29, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 323-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Oct 8 (Box 29, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 325-26.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Oct 12 (Box 29, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 329-30.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Oct 29 (Box 29, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 332-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Nov 16 (Box 29, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 339-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Nov 30 (Box 29, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 344-46.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Dec 10 (Box 29, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 348-50.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1782 Dec 28 (Box 29, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 351-53.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Jan 28 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 358-60.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Feb 16 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 366-67.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Feb 25 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 374-76.
      With enclosure: MS 'abstract' of a letter about the earthquake in Calabria.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Mar 8 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 382-85.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1783 Mar 13 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 387-88.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Mar 18 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 388-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Apr 5 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 393-95.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Apr 26 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 395-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 May 27 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 404-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Jun 5 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 411-12.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Jun 28 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 414-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Jul 12 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 420-21.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Aug 2 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 425-26.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Sep 6 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 429-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Oct 10 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 434-36.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Nov 18 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 441-44.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1783 Dec 13 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 456-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Jan 10 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 464-66.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Jan 24 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 467-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Jan 31 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 469-70.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Feb 14 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 473-75.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Mar 13 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 478-81.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Apr 9 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 492-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 May 22 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 498-500.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Jun 26 (Box 30, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 504-5.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Jul 24 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 511-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Jul 31 (Box 30, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 514-15.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Sep 11 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 521-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Sep 18 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 524-27.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Oct 8 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 533-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1784 Dec 18 (Box 30, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 548-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 Jan 4 (Box 30, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 553-55.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 Feb 8 (Box 30, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 559-61.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 Mar 15 (Box 30, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 567-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 May 12 (Box 30, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 580-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 Jun 7 (Box 30, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 585-88.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 Jul 5 (Box 30, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 592-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 Aug 8 (Box 30, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 597-98.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1785 Aug 20 (Box 30, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 25, p. 599-602.